Guide to the Charles Edward Clark Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Charles Edward Clark papers
1900-1968
1935-1963
MS 1344
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
59.75
(145 boxes)
The bulk of the papers date from 1935-1963 and reflect Clark's position as reporter on the United States Supreme Court's Advisory Committee on Rules for Civil Procedure (1935-1956) and as associate judge of the Court of Appeal for the Second Circuit (1939-1963). The papers contain his files for the Committee on Rules for Civil Procedure including preparatory papers, committee proceedings, rule draft reports and correspondence. His years on the Second Circuit Court are documented with complete case and motion files, docket books and correspondence. Also in the papers are extensive research files on law administration, automobile accidents, Puerto Rican courts and the reorganization of state departments in Connecticut. Clark served on Connecticut commissions in 1935-1936 and 1949-1951. His voluminous correspondence (ca. 9 feet) with local and political figures spans the years 1920-1963 and includes Benjamin Cardozo, Felix Frankfurter, Augustus Hand, Learned Hand, Oliver Wendell Holmes, Milton Friedman, James W. Moore, Franklin D. Roosevelt and Harlan Stone. There is only a small amount of personal correspondence or papers from his law school career, either as student, professor or dean. (For this period, see the Yale University Archives.) There are, however, family records, financial papers, account books, photographs, biographical newspaper clippings and a bibliography of his work compiled by Solomon Smith in 1968.
Clark, Charles Edward, 1889-1963
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Charles E. Clark, circa 1940-1959 and of Elias Clark, 1982; transfer from Law School Library, 1983, 2013.
The materials in Series IV, relating to the United States Supreme Court Advisory Committee on Rules for Civil Procedure, were donated to the Yale University Library by Charles E. Clark during the 1940's and 50's. The bulk of the papers, Series I, II, III, V, and VI were donated to the Yale University Library by Elias Clark in 1982.
Scope and Contents
The documentation for Clark's career prior to his appointment to the Second Circuit Court of Appeals in 1939 is fragmentary. Only a few pieces of memorabilia and correspondence have survived from his six years (1913-1919) of private law practice. From his years as a faculty member and Dean of the Yale Law School (1919-1939) approximately five inches of correspondence and several sections of research files have been preserved. The bulk of his administrative files as Dean are missing and presumed to have been destroyed. Researchers interested in the academic portion of Clark's career should consult the records of University Presidents James R. Angell and Charles Seymour; the University Provosts; and the members of the Law School Faculty.
Fortunately, the records relating to Clark's work as reporter for the United States Supreme Court's Advisory Committee on Civil Procedure (1935-1956) have survived intact.
In marked contrast to the materials from Clark's academic career, the documentation for his years on the Second Circuit Court of Appeals is both detailed and extensive.
The Clark Papers are organized in six series:
Series I GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE
Series II UNITED STATES COURT OF APPEALS FOR THE SECOND DISTRICT 1939-1963
Series III RESEARCH FILES
Series IV UNITED STATES SUPREME COURT ADVISORY COMMITTEE ON RULES FOR CIVIL PROCEDURE 1935-1936
Series V BIBLIOGRAPHY AND WRITINGS
Series VI PERSONAL CORRESPONDENCE, MEMORABILIA, FAMILY PAPERS
The materials in Series I, GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE 1920-1963, are subdivided into two sections. Correspondence 1920-1939 contains the relatively few letters which have survived from Clark's pre-Court of Appeals career and includes the correspondence relating to his court appointment. Correspondents of note include Benjamin Cardozo, Homer Cummings, Felix Frankfurter, Oliver Wendell Holmes, Franklin D. Roosevelt (telegrams), and Harlan Stone.
Correspondence 1939-1963 reflects Clark's interest and work on a broad range of legal and judicial issues. The correspondence was written and received in his capacity as a lawyer and judge, but it is not specifically concerned with Second Circuit work (see below, Series II). Among the correspondents of note are: Thurman Arnold, Edwin Borchard, Jerome Davis, William O. Douglas, Felix Frankfurter, James W. Moore, Eugene Rostow, Frederick Rodell, Potter Stewart, and Harlan Stone.
Series II, UNITED STATES COURT OF APPEALS FOR THE SECOND DISTRICT 1939-1963, provides virtually complete documentation of Clark's years on the court. The records are subdivided into eight sections:
Docket books
Case files
Motion files
Correspondence with Court of Appeals judges
General court business correspondence
Circuit Council
Judicial Conference
Law Clerks
Series III, RESEARCH FILES, contains correspondence, memoranda, notes, and report drafts relating to Clark's legal research as a scholar and as a member of various research groups and professional committees. The series is subdivided into eleven sections:
Law administration, the National Commission on Law Observance and Enforcement 1929-1933 study of federal law administration.
Social trends, the President's Research Committee on Social Trends' data collection on social change in the United States, 1930-1933. Clark, with William O. Douglas, was principal investigator for law and legal institutions.
Automobile accidents, research conducted during 1929-1933 by the Commission to Study Compensation for Automobile Accidents, under the auspices of the Council for Research in the Social Sciences of Columbia University.
Connecticut Commission on the Reorganization of State Departments, Clark was Vice-Chairman 1935-1936.
Connecticut Legislative Commission on Jails 1931-1938.
American Bar Association, Coordination Committee, 1934-1935 study of plans for reorganizing the American Bar Association.
American Bar Association, Committee on Co-operation with the Bench and Bar, Clark was Chairman 1934-1936.
Puerto Rican Courts, Clark's study of the Puerto Rican judicial system and correspondence with members of the Puerto Rican judiciary and bar association 1949-1963.
Connecticut Commission on State Government Reorganization, 1949-1951 study and report on the Connecticut judicial system directed by Clark.
Institute of Judicial Administration, Inc., 1953-1963, studies, minutes of meetings, correspondence relating to Clark's work as a member of the Institute's Board of Fellows.
Miscellaneous topics including the Connecticut Judicial Council 1927-1930; research memoranda related to the business of federal courts 1934; Code Pleading research notes 1927-1928; National Conference of Commissions on Uniform State Laws, Committee on Corpus and Law, 1927-1933; research notes and memoranda relating to President Roosevelt's plan for reorganization of the Supreme Court, 1937.
Series IV, THE UNITED STATES SUPREME COURT ADVISORY COMMITTEE ON RULES FOR CIVIL PROCEDURE, contains the papers related to Clark's work as committee reporter 1935-1956. The records include preparatory papers, committee proceedings, rule drafts reports, and correspondence arranged in three chronological subdivisions: 1935-1939, 1943-1950, and 1952-1956.
Series V, BIBLIOGRAPHY AND WRITINGS, contains a copy of a bibliography of Clark's work compiled by Solomon Smith in 1968 and several drafts of addresses and articles. Copies of the bulk of Clark's writings are not present in the series, but are accessible through normal bibliographic channels.
Series VI, PERSONAL CORRESPONDENCE, MEMORABILIA, FAMILY RECORDS, is subdivided into ten sections: Personal Correspondence 1915-1962, much of which concerns routine family and personal business; Correspondence of Dorothy Clark 1955-1967, containing letters from Thurman Arnold and a series of letters from Clark's friends and associates after his death, commenting on the significance of his work; Testimonials and resolutions, by professional and academic groups in honor of Clark; Photographs, primarily portraits and of Clark with colleagues and associates; Law School examinations, given by Clark while a faculty member; School and professional memorabilia; Biographical newspaper clippings 1907-1963, useful for an overview of Clark's many professional activities; Financial records; Family records; and Diplomas and award certificates.
Biographical / Historical
Charles Edward Clark was born in Woodbridge, Connecticut on December 9, 1889, the son of Samuel Orman and Pauline C. Marquand Clark. He graduated from Yale College in 1911 and Yale Law School in 1913; in the same year he was admitted to the Connecticut bar.
In 1919, after six years of private practice in New Haven, Clark was appointed to the faculty of the Yale Law School as assistant professor. He was promoted to associate professor in 1922, full professor in 1923, the Lines Professorship in 1927, and Sterling Professor of Law in 1929.
He served as Dean of the Law School from 1929 to 1939, one of the most productive and critical periods in the School's history. The Sterling Law Buildings were completed in 1931 and the Faculty of Law expanded. Clark's term as Dean was notable for a reorganization of the School's curriculum to place more emphasis on the social functions of the law, including the interrelation between law and commerce, sociology, medicine, psychology, and economics.
Clark was active in Connecticut politics and served on several committees seeking to improve the State's administrative and judicial systems; these included the Commission on Reorganization of State Executive Departments 1935-1936 and the Commission on State Government Reorganization 1949-1951.
Nationally, Clark was best known for his service on the United States Supreme Court's Advisory Committee on Civil Procedure from 1935 to 1956. In his capacity as committee reporter he became the principal architect of the Federal Rules of Civil Procedure, which were adopted for all Federal trial courts and copied by many state courts.
In 1939 he was appointed associate judge of the United States Court of Appeal for the Second Circuit (New York, Connecticut, and Vermont). From 1954 to 1959 he was chief judge of the Court. He resumed his seat as associate judge until his death on December 13, 1963.
Clark was the author of numerous articles and books, including Code Pleading, 1928; Real Covenants, 1929; and Cases on Pleading and Procedure, 2 vols. 1930, 1933.
For further biographical detail see the section of biographical newspaper clippings 1907-1963 in Series VI.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in six series and three additions: I. General Correspondence, 1920-1963. II. United States Court of Appeals for the Second District, 1939-1963. III. Research files, 1929-1963. IV. United States Supreme Court Advisory Comittee on Rules for Civil Procedure, 1935-1956. V. Bibliography and writings, 1926-1968. VI. Personal correspondence, memorabilia, family records, 1907-1967.
Law; Connecticut -- Politics and government; Puerto Rico -- Politics and government; Account books; Photoprints; Judges; Lawyers; Acheson, Dean, 1893-1971; Arnold, Truman; Borchard, Edwin, 1884-1951; Cardozo, Benjamin N. (Benjamin Nathan), 1870-1938; Clark, Charles Edward, 1889-1963; Clark, Mary D.; Clark, Pauline C. Marquard; Clark, Samuel Orman, 1900-1975; Clark, Samuel Orman, 1900-1975; Countryman, Vern, 1917-; Davis, Jerome, 1891-1979; Douglas, William O. (William Orville), 1898-1980; Fordham, Jefferson B., 1905-1994; Fortas, Abe, 1910-1982; Frank, Jerome, 1889-1957; Frankfurter, Felix, 1882-1965; Friedman, Milton, 1912-2006; Gulliver, Ashbel Green, 1897-; Hand, Augustus Noble, 1869-1954; Hand, Chauncey Harris, 1893-1961; Hand, Learned, 1872-1961; Hincks, Carroll Clark, 1889-1964; Holmes, Oliver Wendell, 1809-1894; Hutchins, Robert Maynard, 1899-1977; Jackson, Robert, b. 1880; Kaufman, Irving R. (Irving Robert), 1910-1992; Kefauver, Estes, 1903-1963; Laski, Harold J. (Harold Joseph), 1893-1950; Lumbard, J. Edward (Joseph Edward), 1901-1999; Marshall, Thurgood, 1908-1993; McDougal, Myres S. (Myres Smith), 1906-1998; Medina, Harold R. (Harold Raymond), 1888-1990; Moore, James William, 1905-1994; Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945; Smith, J. Joseph, 1904-; Stewart, Potter; Stone, Harlan Fiske, 1872-1946; Swan, Thomas W. (Thomas Walter), 1877-1975; Waterman, Sterry R.; Wright, Charles Alan, 1927-2000; Clark family; United States. Supreme Court; Yale Law School; Yale University -- Faculty
- Correspondence, 1920-1963; Series I; 8' (20 boxes)
  Scope and Contents
  Series I is subdivided into two sections: General Correspondence 1920-1939 and General Correspondence 1939-1963. Within each section materials are arranged alphabetically. The number of letters from major correspondents is contained in parentheses before inclusive dates.
  - General Correspondence 1920-1939
    - Cardozo, Benjamin (5), 1924 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Cummings, Homer (3), 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Frankfurter, Felix (4), 1923-1926 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Hand, Augustus (1), 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Hand, Learned (1), 1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      General note
      see also: box 63, folder 320
    - Holmes, Oliver Wendell (5), 1921-1931 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D. (2), 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Seymour, Charles (1), 1939 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Stone, Harlan (4), 1923-1924 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Sacco and Vanzetti case (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Unites States Department of Justice Antitrust Division, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - A (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - B (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - C-F (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - G-L (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - M-R (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - S-T (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - U-Z (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - General Correspondence 1939-1963
    - A, 1939-1956 (Box 1, Folder 19-20)
    - A, 1957-1963 (Box 2, Folder 21-23)
    - A, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - A, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Acheson, Dean (2), 1940 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Allen, Florence (1), 1948-1960 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Arnold, Thurman (25), 1939-1963 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - American Judicature Society, 1953-1963 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - American Jewish Committee, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Appellate Rules Committee, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Association of the Bar of the City of New York, 1955-1961 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - B, 1939-1961 (Box 2, Folder 31-34)
    - B, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Baldwin, Raymond (2), 1940-1959 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Biddle, Francis (3), 1941-1945 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Bittker, Boris (3), 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Biggs, John Jr., 1957 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Black, Hugo (2), 1952 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Blair, Edwin (2), 1963 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Borchard, Edwin (8), 1941-1945 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Bowles, Chester (1), 1950 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Brennan, William J. Jr. (1), 1957 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - C, 1939-1952 (Box 3, Folder 45-48)
    - C, 1953-1963 (Box 4, Folder 49-53)
    - Chaffee, Zachariah Jr. (2), 1920, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Cooper, Irving (2), 1954 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Countryman, Vern (10), 1958-1963 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Clark, Samuel O., Jr. (43), 1937-1943 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Clark, Samuel O., Jr. (35), 1945-1948 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Callaghan & Co., 1935-1963 (Box 5, Folder 59-61)
    - D, 1939-1963 (Box 5, Folder 62-65)
    - Davis, Jerome (21), 1940-1962 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Douglas, William O. (11), 1939-1947 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - E, 1939-1953, 1957-1961 (Box 6, Folder 68-70)
    - Emerson, Thomas I. (1), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - F, 1939-1963 (Box 6, Folder 73-78)
    - Fleming, James (1), 1959 (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - Fordham, Jefferson (18), 1949-1960 (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - Fortas, Abe (3), 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Frank, Jerome N. (1), 1941 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Frankfurter, Felix (11), 1940-1956 (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - Friedman, Milton (5), 1945-1952 (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - G, 1939-1963 (Box 7, Folder 85-90)
    - Griswold, Erwin Griswold, Whitney (3), 1939-1963 (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - Goldstein, Abe (2), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - Gulliver, A. G. (12), 1940-1945 (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - H, 1939-1948 (Box 7, Folder 94-95)
    - H, 1949-1953, 1957-1963 (Box 8, Folder 96-100)
    - Hand, Chauncey Jr. (8), 1939-1961 (Box 8, Folder 101)
    - Harper, Fowler (1), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 102)
    - Hicks, Frederick (3), 1940-1941 (Box 8, Folder 103)
    - Hincks, Carroll (6), 1930-1949 (Box 8, Folder 104)
      see also: box 64, folder 330
    - Hutchins, Robert, 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 105)
    - I, 1939-1961 (Box 8, Folder 106-109)
    - J, 1939-1963 (Box 9, Folder 110-114)
    - Jackson, Robert (5), 1940 (Box 9, Folder 115)
    - K, 1939-1963 (Box 9, Folder 116-120)
    - Katz, Wilbur (1), 1948 (Box 9, Folder 121)
    - Kaufman, Irving (6), 1952-1959 (Box 9, Folder 122)
    - Kefauver, Estes (2), 1951-1956 (Box 9, Folder 123)
    - Kessler, Friedrich (1), 1934-1945 (Box 9, Folder 124)
    - L, 1939-1948 (Box 9, Folder 125)
    - L, 1949-1963 (Box 10, Folder 126-130)
    - Ladies Aid (Box 10, Folder 131)
    - La Follette, Robert Jr. (1), 1939 (Box 10, Folder 132)
    - Laski, Harold (1), 1937-1953 (Box 10, Folder 133)
    - Lasswell, Harold, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 134)
    - Levi, Edward (1), 1950-1951 (Box 10, Folder 135)
    - Llewellyn, Karl (2), 1945-1962 (Box 10, Folder 136)
    - M, 1939-1952 (Box 10, Folder 137-140)
    - M, 1953-1954, 1957-1963 (Box 11, Folder 141-144)
    - Maloney, Francis (2), 1940-1941 (Box 11, Folder 145)
    - Medina, Charles (3), 1950-1952 (Box 11, Folder 146)
    - Moore, James W. (30), 1941-1950 (Box 11, Folder 147)
    - Mc, 1939-1956 (Box 11, Folder 148-149)
    - McDougal, Myres (7), 1940-1952 (Box 11, Folder 150)
    - N, 1939-1954 (Box 11, Folder 151-153)
    - N, 1955-1963 (Box 12, Folder 154-157)
    - Northrop, Filmer, 1940-1954 (Box 12, Folder 158)
    - O, 1939-1963 (Box 12, Folder 159-164)
    - Phi Beta Kappa Association, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 165-166)
    - P, 1939-1963 (Box 13, Folder 167-172)
    - Pepper, George (4), 1940-1961 (Box 13, Folder 173)
    - Pierson, George (3), 1944 (Box 13, Folder 174)
    - Powell, Thomas, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 175)
    - Q, 1946-1954 (Box 13, Folder 176)
    - R, 1939-1959 (Box 13, Folder 177-180)
    - R, 1960-1963 (Box 14, Folder 181-182)
    - Rodell, Fred (12), 1941-1950 (Box 14, Folder 183)
    - Rostow, Eugene (11), 1946-1962 (Box 14, Folder 184)
    - Roosevelt Presidential Library Executive Committee, 1938-1941 (Box 14, Folder 185)
    - S, 1939-1959 (Box 14, Folder 186-190)
    - S, 1960-1963 (Box 15, Folder 191-192)
    - Seymour, Charles (4), 1940-1962 (Box 15, Folder 193)
    - Shafroth, Will (Country Club) (9), 1960-1963 (Box 15, Folder 194)
    - Shulman, Harry (3), 1941-1954 (Box 15, Folder 195)
    - Smith, Reginald (1), 1947 (Box 15, Folder 196)
    - Sobeloff, Simon, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 197)
    - Stewart, Potter (5), 1958-1961 (Box 15, Folder 198)
    - Stone, Harlan (5), 1939-1943 (Box 15, Folder 199)
    - Sturges, Wesley (1), 1944-1963 (Box 15, Folder 200)
    - Swaine, Robert (2), 1948 (Box 15, Folder 201)
    - T, 1939-1963 (Box 15, Folder 202-205)
    - U, 1939-1961 (Box 16, Folder 206-212)
    - U, 1962-1963 (Box 17, Folder 213)
    - V, 1939-1963 (Box 17, Folder 214-219)
    - W, 1936, 1939-1959 (Box 17, Folder 220-223)
    - W, 1960-1963 (Box 18, Folder 224-225)
    - Warren, Earl, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 226)
    - Wilder, Thornton (1), 1957 (Box 18, Folder 227)
    - Wright, Charles A. (34), 1952-1963 (Box 18, Folder 228-229)
    - Wright, Skelly (1), 1962 (Box 18, Folder 230)
    - West Publishing Co., 1939-1952 (Box 18, Folder 231-235)
    - West Publishing Co., 1953-1963 (Box 19, Folder 236-237)
    - XYZ, 1939-1963 (Box 19, Folder 238-242)
    - Reprints (Recipients of) (Box 19, Folder 243)
    - Yale Law School Curriculum Committee: memoes to, 1932, undated (Box 19, Folder 244)
    - Yale Law School - History (Box 19, Folder 245)
    - Yale Law School, 1961-1963 (Box 20, Folder 246)
    - Yale Law School Association, 1962-1963 (Box 20, Folder 247)
    - Yale Law School Capital Funds Program (Box 20, Folder 248)
- United States Court of Appeals for the Second District, 1939-1963; Series II; 23' (55 boxes)
  The materials in Series II are organized in eight sections:
  Docket books
  Case files
  Motion files
  Correspondence with Court of Appeals judges
  General court business correspondence
  Circuit Council
  Judicial Conference
  Law Clerks
  - Docket Books
    - 1938-1942 (Box 21, Folder 1-4)
    - 1942-1946 (Box 22, Folder 5-8)
    - 1946-1951 (Box 23, Folder 9-12)
    - 1951-1954 (Box 24, Folder 13-15)
    - 1954-1958 (Box 25, Folder 16-19)
    - 1958-1962 (Box 26, Folder 20-23)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 27, Folder 24-25)
    - Vol. 1 1939 Mar 20-1949 Jun 30 Part 1 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Vol. 1 1939 Mar 20-1949 Jun 30 Part 2 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Vol. 1 1939 Mar 20-1949 Jun 30 Part 3 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Vol. 1 1939 Mar 20-1949 Jun 30 Part 4 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Vol. 2 1949 Oct 1-1954 Jun 30 Part 1 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Vol. 2 1949 Oct 1-1954 Jun 30 Part 2 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Vol. 2 1949 Oct 1-1954 Jun 30 Part 3 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Vol. 3 1954 Oct 1-1956 Jun 30 Part 1 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - Vol. 3 1954 Oct 1-1956 Jun 30 Part 2 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - Vol. 3 1954 Oct 1-1956 Jun 30 Part 3 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Vol. 4 1956 Aug - 1963 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Case Files
    - 1938-1939 A-E (Box 29, Folder 37)
    - 1938-1939 F-J (Box 29, Folder 38)
    - 1938-1939 K-N (Box 29, Folder 39)
    - 1938-1939 O-T (Box 29, Folder 40)
    - 1938-1939 U-Z (Box 29, Folder 41)
    - 1939-1940 A-E (Box 29, Folder 42)
    - 1939-1940 F-L (Box 29, Folder 43)
    - 1939-1940 M-S (Box 29, Folder 44)
    - 1939-1940 T-Z (Box 29, Folder 45)
    - 1939-1940 T-Z (Box 29, Folder 46)
    - 1940-1941 A-F (Box 30, Folder 47)
    - 1940-1941 G-L (Box 30, Folder 48)
    - 1940-1941 M-R (Box 30, Folder 49)
    - 1940-1941 S-U (Box 30, Folder 50)
    - 1940-1941 V-Z (Box 30, Folder 51)
    - 1941-1942 A-E (Box 30, Folder 52)
    - 1941-1942 F-K (Box 30, Folder 53)
    - 1941-1942 L-Q (Box 31, Folder 54)
    - 1941-1942 R-U (Box 31, Folder 55)
    - 1941-1942 V-Z (Box 31, Folder 56)
    - 1942-1943 A-G (Box 31, Folder 57)
    - 1942-1943 H-M (Box 31, Folder 58)
    - 1942-1943 N-T (Box 31, Folder 59)
    - 1942-1943 U-Z (Box 31, Folder 60)
    - 1942-1943 U-Z (Box 31, Folder 61)
    - 1943-1944 A-E (Box 31, Folder 62)
    - 1943-1944 F-J (Box 32, Folder 63)
    - 1943-1944 K-N (Box 32, Folder 64)
    - 1943-1944 O-T (Box 32, Folder 65)
    - 1943-1944 U-Z (Box 32, Folder 66)
    - 1943-1944 U-Z (Box 32, Folder 67)
    - 1944-1945 A-F (Box 32, Folder 68)
    - 1944-1945 A-F (Box 32, Folder 69)
    - 1944-1945 G-M (Box 32, Folder 70)
    - 1944-1945 N-S (Box 33, Folder 71)
    - 1944-1945 T-U (Box 33, Folder 72)
    - 1944-1945 T-U (Box 33, Folder 73)
    - 1944-1945 V-Z (Box 33, Folder 74)
    - 1945-1946 A-E (Box 33, Folder 75)
    - 1945-1946 F-L (Box 33, Folder 76)
    - 1945-1946 M-R (Box 33, Folder 77)
    - 1945-1946 S-U (Box 34, Folder 78)
    - 1945-1946 V-Z (Box 34, Folder 79)
    - 1946-1947 A-D (Box 34, Folder 80)
    - 1946-1947 E-L (Box 34, Folder 81)
    - 1946-1947 M-Q (Box 34, Folder 82)
    - 1946-1947 R-T (Box 34, Folder 83)
    - 1946-1947 U-Z (Box 34, Folder 84)
    - 1947-1948 A-D (Box 34, Folder 85)
    - 1947-1948 E-K (Box 35, Folder 86)
    - 1947-1948 L-R (Box 35, Folder 87)
    - 1947-1948 S-T (Box 35, Folder 88)
    - 1947-1948 U-Z (Box 35, Folder 89)
    - 1947-1948 U-Z (Box 35, Folder 90)